But this is cool. You have actually a
working game already.
>> Opus 4.8 dropped last week. We are using
every day like we are addicted to it and
it's kind of fun to play with it. Is it
the best model ever created? We are
going to check that in this video right
now. Subscribe like the video and share
it to your friend because they need to
watch us. I want to build an FPS arena
like it's it should be like a first
person shooter game to demo 4.8. Okay.
Ajon demo. No, I want to do the FPS
first. So, I have the prompt ready. So,
nothing have been set up. It's just
going to go like end from scratch. Just
going to take that the FPS arena build
FPS arena end to end a playable browser
firsterson shooter arena with React
TypeScript and VIT whatever whatever and
3GS 3GS pointer blah blah blah.
>> Okay. What effort do you have enabled
right now? [clears throat] And we are
going to do that with max. So that
should be ultra mode, right?
>> Yeah. Well, I I never I always do it in
terminal. But
>> yes,
>> instead of the prompt, if you do
slasheffort, does it show you the to do
the selection as well?
>> No, because the effort is in the to
right. Yes. So I don't have the the is
max ultra mode for sure response but
takes longer. Okay, let me check if I
should use the the terminal instead of
and we won't. Okay, so Max was not even
>> Yeah, Max was rainbow
>> and boom.
>> Nice.
See, and here it says it's XI plus a
dynamic.
>> Yes.
>> Overflow orchestration.
>> Nice.
>> Oh, workflow orchestration.
>> Okay, back. Am I? No, I mean F. Let's go
back to Dragon Ball Z. Back.
Okay. So,
uh FB FPS arena blah blah blah. Okay.
So, let's see what it goes. Um so, like
you can do that all the time.
Dev Dev server live at local host. Let's
go.
>> Okay. Share it.
>> Window FPS arena.
Okay.
So, move, fire, left click. Okay. All
for auto jump, reload. Okay.
>> Oh,
but this is cool. You have actually a
working game already.
>> Jesus.
Oh, there was a bug. He walked right
through the pillar.
>> Yeah, there is no collision yet.
>> Yeah,
>> but maybe we can fix that. Score kills
enemies.
>> Yeah, it it counts it all.
>> That's crazy. That's kind of cool.
And see there is the lights effect. Oh,
no. Okay. It's the when the when it
dies.
But this is like before people used to
code on something like Juke Nug or
whatever like or Quake.
>> Yeah.
>> Forever and now you have it in a few
minutes.
>> And there is like ammunition too. You
don't see it but I have the counter of
ammunition
like the amos.
I can reloading.
That's nuts.
Okay. 15 second. Okay. What? What? Okay.
Game over. I died.
>> Do you also have a scoreboard right now?
>> Score.
No.
>> No.
>> Pause. There is a pause.
Health
and ammunition.
And I can reload. And it's reloading.
Mhm. [clears throat] Boom.
That's kind of sick, man. In [snorts] 18
minutes, we have something that works.
That's cool. And now it's just
optimizing.
>> Yeah.
>> Make this better. Make this better. Give
me an option to swap guns or whatever.
>> Add a reloading animation.
Time out. FPS verify. Verify
point locker error gun. Okay. Okay. Uh
scene is non blank. A truly blank canva.
Yellow. Okay. Whatever. The arena render
beautifully. floor grind and with death
glowing tire wall blah blah blah. This
is exactly right. The first screen is
the game and in game start over with
control click to play blah blah blah.
>> So this is actually what they said that
Opus 4.8 they would do. You give it a
prompt and it decides on each subtask.
>> Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. Like the user
added new requirement made task. So it's
it was not even done. My verification
baseline is green then implement all of
the new features.
It doesn't before it would just start
coding or whatever you ask and now I
said no no no we can start we need to do
some checks first make sure that all
works and then we can proceed.
>> I like that.
>> Yeah that that makes it look so much
better
and it's even managing. Yeah I I I saw
that before with like 4.7 but like yeah
nesting almost done thinking with XI
effort so it during the task it's also
able to change the effort.
>> Yeah. So this now we are happy with Opus
4.8, right? This is a good result.
>> I mean that's definitely impressive.
But should we wait a bit again? I we
could build mobile games.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. This is something you
could play on mobile.
>> It's building. It's building everything.
Checking if there is any errors. Reload
bar. Reload bar. Banner. That looks like
Okay. Boss boss bar wraps. [laughter]
If that works, that's going to be sick.
>> Oh, you have the laser beam.
>> I think we had it before.
>> And you have your And now we can see
your health bar and your uh
>> Yes, but because I resized the WL.
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> There is animation. Oh, there is.
>> Yeah, for reloading.
>> Okay, wait. I want the collisions. Check
>> here. See, it walks around. that can't
go through anymore.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. We have to
That's so [__] cool.
>> Okay. We're almost at the boss.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Two left.
One left.
>> We We should have bonus and new weapons,
too. Bro, we are building a a game.
Oh, it's a bigger one.
>> Okay, just a bigger one. Yeah,
>> bro. That's sick.
>> Now, the question is, does it do more
damage as well?
>> Oh, yeah, it does. [laughter]
>> That's so
>> Oh, you're out of time.
>> No. No. Oh, did I? No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No. Oh, it reset it because
you
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Bro,
I want to continue this game. This is
sick.
>> This is cool.
>> Update value. So, the change is live yet
the boss still render brown. What?
The pixel is identical to the boss body.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, and
give me upgrades, new weapons that I can
drop. And I can pick up after I kill mob
and make the mob fire back.
Upgrade. Oh,
French accent.
Uh, upgrading.
>> If you did too much friends accent if I
give it like a French mustache.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Give me upgrades.
nes
new weapon
that I can pick up after kill the mob
and make make the mobs
fire back
and add some skills for the boss
shield
faster
movement movement etc. Uh, the boss
Norander has a clear maning bright red
giant with glowing eyes, its own
floating hers. Okay, so we already had
that.
>> Yeah, we already had a test harness
artifact prefilled the magazine. What?
One check regressed, bro. It's It's
That's cool because the full testing the
full pipeline
and it's been 40 minutes already. [__]
>> Mhm.
>> Okay. Time goes fast when you're having
fun.
>> Yeah.
>> Pick up health, ammo, damage, pick up
produce,
enemy range, blah blah blah. Boss shield
duration and rage.
>> Oh, you you make it bad.
>> Projectile damage, projectile speed,
barrage count, bar. What? Barrage
spread. What's barrage? Toast. Small
transient toast for pickup. Shotgun.
Let's go. Okay, we need to test that.
We're not We're not We're not
>> That's a finale.
>> That's exactly. Okay, I'm going to stop
the other apps because I want my weekly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You want to make sure that
this can be finished.
>> Yeah. Replace. Okay. That's kind of
interesting though because
confirm refuted. So, it refused
some binding and fixes.
It's It looks like ship code but
integrated to the CLA. Replace FPS
arena. Bam. I'm going to give you
move. Look. Okay. Switch weapon. Switch
weapon. Okay. We have the weapon.
>> Mhm.
>> One, two, three, four. Okay.
So,
okay. I don't have weapons.
Oh,
>> shotgun. Okay.
>> And double damage.
>> Okay. Where is the rifle? Rifle.
Shotgun. It's a
>> Okay. That's cool.
>> Weapon, but
Oh, they fired. They fire back.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, and it Oh, you're
adding health.
>> Yeah.
>> You need to get closer for your shotgun.
>> SMG. SMG SMG SMG SMG2
Okay, it's changed the colors of the
>> of the top of your gun.
>> Yeah. Okay,
>> that's a cannon.
>> Cannon. Cannon.
I need
Okay. Okay. That's getting That's
getting crazy.
I should have had music. [__]
[laughter]
I don't like the cannon too. Okay.
Health buff rifle SMG
and [clears throat] see like the damage
is less.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But it's faster. No, it's lit, bro.
Can we do that? Could we have done that
before? I have never tried it, but I
know that game studios doing this setup,
it takes them a few days to do it
properly.
>> I think.
>> Yeah.
>> Like with 3GS?
>> No, without AI.
>> Oh, yeah. No, but I mean like Yeah. It's
not It's not clear obscure neither,
right? Like,
>> okay, let's see how good the end is.
>> The boss. The boss. The boss.
>> Not the shotgun. That's too far away.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it's managed by
that.
He has a
>> Oh, he has the shield
>> cannon. Cannon is lit.
[snorts]
[laughter]
>> More. My god, that's lit. Okay, but
Okay, so the shield is if I'm too close.
>> Yeah, the shield kicks in.
>> I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
>> Almost. Almost.
Okay, I can use that. Wait, I got it.
Yes.
>> Oh, that was cool.
>> That's
amazing. I had fun, bro.
>> I would say that was a successful test.
>> Yes, that was lit. 4.8. Yeah, 4.8 is
lit.
>> Yes, we like it. So, the question is,
are you going to create full-time
Minecraft games?
>> I don't have time, man. I don't have
time.
But it could be a a real option.
>> Mitch, thank you so much for your time.
>> Yeah, thank you for using your tokens
for us.
>> Yes, my pleasure. I will post this the
code
to to the GitHub like the YouTube
channel repository.
>> Yeah, push the game as well so people
can modify it.
>> We could we could even like add more Oh,
we could work with it with codeex.
>> Mhm. and [clears throat] add
multiplayers and stuff like that. If we
can use room and then a score scoreboard
blah blah blah, that would be
>> that would be sick. Yeah.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's talk about it.
Let's talk about it.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you so much for your time,
everyone. Uh thank you for watching the
video. Like, subscribe, and we will see
you next week.
>> Have a nice evening, a nice day.
>> Bye. bye.